A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, General Correspondence FA735
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1957
  - Vaughan…, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - Veterans…, 1957 (Reel C-1245)
  - Villa…, 1957 (Reel C-1246)
  - Virginia…, 1957 (Reel C-1246)
  - Virginia, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1246)
  - Von…, 1957 (Reel C-1246)
  - WA – WZ [General File]: WA – Wohl, 1957 (Reel C-1246)
  - WA – WZ [General File]: Wohl – WZ, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Wachs, Melvin, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Wagner…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Walker…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Wallace…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Ward, F. Champion, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Ward…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Warner…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Warsaw, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Washington, University of (Seattle), 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Washington, University of (St. Louis), 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Washington…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Watson…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Wayne State University, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Weaver, Fred H., 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Weaver…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Weisblat, Abraham, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Wesley Foundation, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - West Virginia University, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - West…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Western College Association, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Western College for Women, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Western…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Wetter, J. Gillis, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - Wheeler…, 1957 (Reel C-1247)
  - White…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Who's Who…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Williams…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Willis…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Wilmington College, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Wilson…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Winchester…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Wisconsin Taxpayers Alliance, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Wisconsin, University of, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Wolf…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Wood…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Woman's…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - World Affairs, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - World Association of World Federalist, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - World Education Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - World Federation for Mental Health, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - World Health Organization, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - World Tape Pals, Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - World Vision Inc., 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - Wright…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - World…, 1957 (Reel C-1248)
  - XA – XZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1249)
  - YA – YZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1249)
  - Yale University, 1957 (Reel C-1249)
  - Young…, 1957 (Reel C-1249)
  - YMCA (Young Men's Christian Association), 1957 (Reel C-1249)
  - Yugoslavia, 1957 (Reel C-1249)
  - ZA – ZZ [General File], 1957 (Reel C-1249)
  - Zamorski, Lucien, 1957 (Reel C-1249)
  - Zawodny, Jan K., 1957 (Reel C-1249)
  - Zimmerman…, 1957 (Reel C-1249)
  - Bibliography of Related Materials, General Correspondence, 1957 (Reel C-1249)
    List of books, pamphlets, articles, reports, etc. related to the General Correspondence files for 1957.
- General Correspondence, 1958
  A bibliography of related books, pamphlets, articles, reports, etc. related to the General Correspondence files for 1958 is filed at the end of this series.
  - AA – AZ [General File]: AA – Albany Institute, 1958 (Reel C-1249)
  - AA – AZ [General File]: Albany – AZ, 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Accrediting Association of Bible Colleges, 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Action-Housing Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Adams…, 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Africa, 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Agriculture, Department of (United States), 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Air Force, United States, 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Alabama, 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Alabama, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Alaska Methodist University, 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Alexander…, 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - Alexander, Ramy, 1958 (Reel C-1250)
  - All Pakistan Women's Association, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - Allen…, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - Allison Mailinglists Corp., 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American…, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American Academy, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American Association of Retired Persons, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American Association…, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American Committee…, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American Council on Education, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American Economic Association, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American Federation of Arts, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American Federation…, 1958 (Reel C-1251)
  - American-Asian Educational Exchange Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Friends…, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Friends of Vietnam, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Institute, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Institute…, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Institute of Planners, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Management Association Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Medical Association, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American National theatre and Academy, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Nurses Association, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Red Cross, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Society…, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Society for Engineering Education, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American University (Cairo), 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - American University (Washington D.C.), 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - Americana Press, 1958 (Reel C-1252)
  - Anderson…, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Andrews…, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Area II (Democracy), 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Area III (Economic Development), 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Area III (Economic Development) – Attachments, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Arena Stage, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Arizona, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Arkansas, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Armed Forces Management Association, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Armour Research Foundation, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Armstrong…, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Arnold, Edwin G., 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Asia, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Askling, John, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Associated…, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Associated…, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Associated Management Services, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association…, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association for Asian Studies, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association of American Law Schools, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association of Canadian Schools of Commerce and Business Administration, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association of Collegiate Schools o Architecture, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association of Hungarian Students in the United States, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association of Radio and Television News Analysts, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association of Research Libraries (ARL), 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Association of Universities of the British Commonwealth, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Atlanta…, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Atlantic…, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Austria, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - Azikiwe, Nnamdi, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - BA – BZ [General File]: BA – Baltzell, 1958 (Reel C-1252A)
  - BA – BZ [General File]: Baltzell –Boris, 1958 (Reel C-1253)
  - BA – BZ [General File]: Boris – BZ, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Bacon…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Bailey…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Baker…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Ball…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Baltimore, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Baro College, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Barnes…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Barnett…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Bartlett…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Bates…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Baylor…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Baylor University, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Beck…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Becker…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Bell…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Bender…, 1958 (Reel C-1254)
  - Benjamin, Ira, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Bennett…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Benson…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Berea College, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Berger, Monroe, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Berlin, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Bernays, Edward L, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Bernstein…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Berry…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Berry Schools, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Bethany…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Beverlage, Lora, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Bishop…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Blaisdell…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Blonder-Tongue, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Board…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Boerstler, Richard W., 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Boston, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Bowdoin College, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Boy Scouts, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Boys…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - British…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Brookings institute, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Brooklyn…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Brooklyn Association for Improving the Condition of the Poor, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Brooklyn Juvenile Guidance Center, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Brooks…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Brown…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Brussels Fair Courier, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Bryant…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Bureau…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Burke…, 1958 (Reel C-1255)
  - Burma, 1958 (Reel C-1255, Reel C-1256)
  - Burness, Carl, 1958 (Reel C-1256)
  - Burns…, 1958 (Reel C-1256)
  - Burrelle's Press Clipping Bureau, 1958 (Reel C-1256)
  - Burton…, 1958 (Reel C-1256)
  - Bush…, 1958 (Reel C-1256)
  - Butler…, 1958 (Reel C-1256)
  - Byrnes, Robert F., 1958 (Reel C-1256)
  - CA – CZ [General File]: CA – Colf, 1958 (Reel C-1256)
  - CA – CZ [General File]: Colf – CZ, 1958 (Reel C-1256)
  - Calcutta University, 1958 (Reel C-1257)
  - California…, 1958 (Reel C-1257)
  - California, University of (Berkeley), 1958 (Reel C-1257)
  - California, University of (Los Angeles), 1958 (Reel C-1257)
  - Calvary…, 1958 (Reel C-1257)
  - Cambridge Repertory Theatre, 1958 (Reel C-1257)
  - Cambridge University, 1958 (Reel C-1257)
  - Camp…, 1958 (Reel C-1257)
  - Campbell…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Canada Council for the Arts, Humanities, and Social Sciences, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Canadian…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Canadian Institute of International Affairs, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carleton…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carlson…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carlucci, Gian Carlo, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carnegie…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carpenter…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carr…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carroll…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carroll, Thomas H., 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Carter…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Case Institute of Technology, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Catholic…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Center…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Central intelligence Agency (CIA), 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Centre…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Chamber…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Chamberlain…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Chang…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Chapman…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Charleston…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Charnes, A., 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Chermayeff, Serge, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Chester…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Chicago…, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Chicago, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1258)
  - Child Research Council, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Childrens…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Choate School…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Christ…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Christian…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Church…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Churchill…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Citizens…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Citizens Conference of Governmental Cooperation, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Claremont…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Clark…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Clarke…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Cleary…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Cleveland…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Cohen…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Cole…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - College…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - College of Advanced Science, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Colombo Plan Council, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Colorado…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Colorado State Planning Division, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Colorado, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Columbia…, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Columbia University, 1958 (Reel C-1259)
  - Committee…, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Committee on the history of Social Welfare, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Committee for Rural Development Program, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Committee for the Study of Mankind, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Community…, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Conference…, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Conference for Corporation Executives, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Conseil Europeen du Comite International de L'Organisation Scientifique [CECIOS / CIOS], 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Contemporary Music Society, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Cook…, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Cooper…, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Cornell College, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Cornell University, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Council…, 1958 (Reel C-1260)
  - Council for Atomic Age Studies, 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - Council for Foreign Relations, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - Crawford…, 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - Culbertson…, 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - Cultural…, 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - Cummings…, 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - Cunningham…, 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - Cunningham, Mildred, 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - Curry…, 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - Curtis…, 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - Cyert, R.M., 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - DA – DZ [General File]: DA – Dolan, 1958 (Reel C-1261)
  - DA – DZ [General File]: Dolan – DZ, 1958 (Reel C-1262)
  - Dallin, David, J., 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Dana…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Daniel…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Daniels…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Dartmouth College, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - David…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - [Leonardo] Da Vinci Association, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Davis…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Dayton Daily News, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Day…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Dean…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Declaration of Atlantic Unity, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - De La Salle…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Denny…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Denver, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare [United States], 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Detroit, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Devi, Maitraye, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Diamond, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Dickinson…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Doxiadis Associates, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Duke University, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Dunbar…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Duncan…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Dunn…, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Dunwoody Industrial Institute, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - E.I. Dupont de Nemours and Co., Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - Duquesne University, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - EA – EZ [General File]: EA – Elliott, 1958 (Reel C-1263)
  - EA – EZ [General File]: Elliott – EZ, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - East…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Eastern…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Eastern Kentucky Regional Planning Commission, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Economic…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Eddison, John c., 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Edison Foundation Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Educational…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Edwards…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Ellis…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Emerson…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Emory University, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Empire State Foundation of Independent Liberal Arts Colleges, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Encyclopedia…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Engel…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - English…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - English-Speaking Union of the Commonwealth, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - English-Speaking Union of the United Sates, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Ensminger, Douglas, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Ernst, Morris L., 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Essex…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - European…, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - European Productivity Agency, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - European Productivity Agency – Attachments, 1958 (Reel C-1264)
  - Evans…, 1958 (Reel C-1265)
  - Evangelical…, 1958 (Reel C-1265)
  - Everett…, 1958 (Reel C-1265)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1958 (Reel C-1265)
  - FA – FZ [General File], 1958 (Reel C-1265)
  - Family…, 1958 (Reel C-1265)
  - Far East-America Council of Commerce and Industry, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Federal…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Federation of Hungarian Former Political Prisoners, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Fekete, Zoltan, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Felix Associates, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Ferguson…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - First…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Fischer…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Fisher…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Flanders, Ralph E., 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Fleming…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Florida…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Florida State University, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Florida, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Food and Agricultural Organization, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Ford…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Fordham…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Foreign…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Fort…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Foster…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Foundation…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Foundation for Research on human Behavior, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Foundation Training Courses and Research, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Fox…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Francis…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Frank…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Franklin…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Franklin Publication, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Free Europe Committee, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Freed…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Freeman…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - French…, 1958 (Reel C-1266)
  - Freund Memorial Foundation, 1958 (Reel C-1267)
  - Friends…, 1958 (Reel C-1267)
  - Frontiers of Science Foundation…, 1958 (Reel C-1267)
  - Fry…, 1958 (Reel C-1267)
  - Frye, Richards N., 1958 (Reel C-1267)
  - Fund…, 1958 (Reel C-1267)
  - GA – GZ [General File]: GA – Gribov, 1958 (Reel C-1267)
  - GA – GZ [General File]: Gribov – GZ, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gaither, H. Rowan, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Galbraith, J.K., 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gant, George F., 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gantt, Edith, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Garcia…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gardner…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - General…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - George…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Georgia…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Ghana…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gibson…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gilbert…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Ginsberg, Norton, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Girl Scouts, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gladstone…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Glasgow, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Goddard College, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Goldberg…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Golden…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Goldstein…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Goncharoff, Nicholas, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gonzaga…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gonzalez…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Good Reading Rack Service, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Goodman…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gordon…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gould…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Governmental Affairs Institute, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Graham…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Gray…, 1958 (Reel C-1268)
  - Great…, 1958 (Reel C-1269)
  - Greater…, 1958 (Reel C-1269)
  - Green…, 1958 (Reel C-1269)
  - Greene…, 1958 (Reel C-1269)
  - Grundstein, Nathan, 1958 (Reel C-1269)
  - Grunwald, Robert, 1958 (Reel C-1269)
  - Guilford…, 1958 (Reel C-1269)
  - Calouste Gulbenkian Foundation, 1958 (Reel C-1269)
  - Gupta…, 1958 (Reel C-1269)
  - HA – HZ [General File]: HA – Herman, 1958 (Reel C-1269)
  - HA – HZ [General File]: Herman – HZ, 1958 (Reel C-1270)
  - Hacker, Frederick J., 1958 (Reel C-1270)
  - Haddad…, 1958 (Reel C-1270)
  - Hall…, 1958 (Reel C-1270)
  - Hamilton…, 1958 (Reel C-1270)
  - Hansen…, 1958 (Reel C-1270)
  - Hanson…, 1958 (Reel C-1270)
  - Harlod, John R., 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Harris…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Harris, Michael S., 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Harrison…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hartford…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Harvard…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Harvard University, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Harvey…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hawaii, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hayes…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Haynes…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hayward…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Heald, Henry T., 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Health…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Henderson…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hendricks…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Henry…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hensel, H. Struve, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hess…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Higgins…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - High…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - High Point Hospital, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hill…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hill, F.F., 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hillside Hospital, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hinckley and Associates, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hirsch…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hispanic Foundation, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Historic…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hitchcock…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Hoffman…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Holland…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Holmes…, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Holmes, Horace, 1958 (Reel C-1271)
  - Holmstrom, Sven, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Holy…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Hood…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Hoover…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Hopkins…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Horn…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Hospital Council of southern California, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - House…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Housing…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Houston…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Howard…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Howard, John B., 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Howell…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Hubbard Association of Scientologists, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Hughes…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Humanities Center for Liberal Education, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Hunt…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Hunter…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Hurwitz…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Hutchinson…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - IA – IZ [General File], 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Idaho…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Illinois…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Illinois, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - Immaculate…, 1958 (Reel C-1272)
  - India…, 1958 (Reel C-1272, Reel C-1273)
  - Indian…, 1958 (Reel C-1273)
  - Indiana…, 1958 (Reel C-1273)
  - Indiana, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1273)
  - Indo-China, 1958 (Reel C-1273)
  - Indonesia…, 1958 (Reel C-1273)
  - Indonesia, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1273)
  - Industrial…, 1958 (Reel C-1273)
  - Institut…, 1958 (Reel C-1273)
  - Institute…, 1958 (Reel C-1273)
  - Institute for Advancement of Medical Communication, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - Institute of International Education, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - Institute for International Order, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - Institute for Mediterranean Affairs, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - Institute of the Pennsylvania Hospital, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - Instituto…, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - Instituto Inter Americano de Ciencias Agricolas, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - Inter…, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - InterAmerican…, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - Inter-University Council for Higher Education Overseas, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - International…, 1958 (Reel C-1274)
  - International Aeronautical Corp., 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Affairs Program, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Cooperation Administration – Attachments, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Forum, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International House, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Labor Advisory Service, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Labor Office, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Legal Studies, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Rescue Committee, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Review of Community Development, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Training and Research (ITR), 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Training and Research (ITR) Fellowships, 1958 (Reel C-1275)
  - International Youth…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Iowa…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Iowa, State University of, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Israel, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Italy, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Iverson, Kenneth R., 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - JA – JZ [General File], 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Jackson…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Jacobi, Werner, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Jacoby, Neil H., 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Jacobs…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Jacobson…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - James…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Japan, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Jargon Books [Jonathan Williams], 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Jensen…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Jewell…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Jewish…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Johns…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Johnson…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)